Some will don't
Some will don't touch
Some will don't touch your
will don't touch your skin,
don't touch your skin, they
touch your skin, they will
your skin, they will hurt
skin, they will hurt people.
they will hurt people. No
will hurt people. No marks
hurt people. No marks outside,
people. No marks outside, but
No marks outside, but chaos
marks outside, but chaos within.
outside, but chaos within. Not
but chaos within. Not every
chaos within. Not every silence
within. Not every silence is
Not every silence is calm,
every silence is calm, not
silence is calm, not every
is calm, not every smile
calm, not every smile is
not every smile is sad.
every smile is sad. Our
smile is sad. Our movement
is sad. Our movement passes
sad. Our movement passes in
Our movement passes in the
movement passes in the brain,
passes in the brain, but
in the brain, but it
the brain, but it still
brain, but it still stays
but it still stays by
it still stays by over
still stays by over you.
stays by over you. That
by over you. That show,
over you. That show, my
you. That show, my enforces
That show, my enforces work,
show, my enforces work, they
my enforces work, they shape
enforces work, they shape the
work, they shape the decisions,
they shape the decisions, they
shape the decisions, they chase
the decisions, they chase the
decisions, they chase the directions,
they chase the directions, they
chase the directions, they rear
the directions, they rear at
directions, they rear at the
they rear at the face
rear at the face of
at the face of you.
the face of you. Now
face of you. Now less
of you. Now less tuning
you. Now less tuning point
Now less tuning point in
less tuning point in your
tuning point in your life,
point in your life, you
in your life, you will
your life, you will be
life, you will be less
you will be less sound.
will be less sound. And
be less sound. And that's
less sound. And that's when
sound. And that's when you
And that's when you realize,
that's when you realize, you
when you realize, you don't
you realize, you don't start
realize, you don't start in
you don't start in silence
don't start in silence before
start in silence before you.
in silence before you.
silence before you.